Hello everyone!
Let's practice the Hey!
Let's practice our "Hey!
Let's do it in three, two, one!
Are you ready, everyone? Let's go!
Ready!
H-I-N-A-T-N-4-T-C!
H.I.N.A.T.N.4.T.C!
Together! Together! Dance with me!
Look at me!
Don't do anything!
Focus with me!
When you're here,
I challenge you to smile!
You'll be born better!
But we're all shy sweet Noonu!
You're here!
And the neighbors too!
Dan! Dan! Dan! Dan! Dan! Dan! Dan!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Let's go!
Love, Nä Your Girl
Hey! Hey! Ohisama
Always, always, always, always...
Stay by my side
Hey!
A-I-N-A-P-A-Pocky
A-I-N-A-P-A-P-A-Pocky
I can go to the world.
Can we go, everybody?
We're all in this body together
I want to sing forever and ever
No, no, no. Let's make a man's noise.
No, no, no, let's leave it in the sun.
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Magical.
I like you now.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The secret of the dead
perchupillow
i willump
chaka chaka chaka
il anu first
As long as we dance together till morning comes
♪ No one will lose me with you
% When the dawn comes, just like in my dreams
# We'll change colors and go looking for it #
# Together with you, together we'll be
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
My voice. Into your voice.
Thank you for watching.
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Stay awake.
Ever, ever, ever, ever, ever
You're perfect for each other
Hey!
A-I-N-A-U-L-O-T-C.
Thank you for everything.
Gratata, Gratata, Gratata.